<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>raunaqness.com</title>
    <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on raunaqness.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://raunaqness.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is bold text, and this is emphasized text.
Visit the Hugo website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Photo credit: Danish Prakash I&amp;rsquo;m Raunaq, I love travel, food, and technology (in that order) (and some other things).
I currently live in Bengaluru and am taking time to explore (read: unemployed) the latest and greatest in AI technologies while contributing to open source projects.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a non-exhaustive list of stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve done over the years:
[2025-Present] Exploring AI Agents, MCP servers, and building side projects to become better at using LLM based tools while contributing to open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Japanese Meal at Kazuko Ramenba, Makati City, Manila, Philippines</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/amazing-japanese-meal-at-kazuko-ramenba-makati-city-manila-philippines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/amazing-japanese-meal-at-kazuko-ramenba-makati-city-manila-philippines/</guid>
      <description>It was my second week in Manila, near the end of my trip. A normal weeknight, but the streets of Makati were still alive with neon lights, music spilling out of bars, and the warm, humid air that wraps around you at night in the Philippines. Around 2 a.m., after a couple of hours of bar-hopping, I found myself wandering—hungry, curious, and not ready to call it a night—when I spotted Kazuko Ramenba glowing invitingly on the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Keema Dosa at Malgudi Mylari Mane, Bangalore, India</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/chicken-keema-dosa-at-malgudi-mylari-mane-bangalore-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/chicken-keema-dosa-at-malgudi-mylari-mane-bangalore-india/</guid>
      <description>Some weekday afternoons call for a little indulgence—and I found mine at Malgudi Mylari Mane in Koramangala. A small, curated menu. Open, airy space. A peek into the spotless kitchen. Everything about it told me I was in good hands.
The star of the show? Their Chicken Keema Dosa. Crisp on the outside, soft inside, and loaded with spiced, juicy chicken keema. It arrived at my table in minutes, yet tasted like something that had been perfected over years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Beef Noodle Soup at Niroumianguan, Seoul, South Korea</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/chinese-beef-noodle-soup-at-niroumianguan-seoul-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/chinese-beef-noodle-soup-at-niroumianguan-seoul-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>During my first week in Seoul, after a blur of Myeongdong street food and too many instant-ramen nights, I opened the Michelin Guide app to find something new. Niroumianguan popped up—nearby and budget-friendly—so I walked 10–15 minutes to check it out.
It&amp;rsquo;s a tiny spot (maybe 10–20 seats) with a memorable décor featuring clean white and vibrant rust colors. The place was fully booked when I arrived, so they asked me to come back the next morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comfort Breakfasts in Hong Kong – Victory A Café &amp; Shine Island Café</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/comfort-breakfasts-in-hong-kong-victory-a-cafe-shine-island-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/comfort-breakfasts-in-hong-kong-victory-a-cafe-shine-island-cafe/</guid>
      <description>On my very first morning in Hong Kong, after arriving late the night before and surviving on just a 7-Eleven snack, I stepped out to explore the streets near my hostel. With no clear plan, I wandered until I spotted Victory A Café—one of those classic local cafés I&amp;rsquo;d read about but never experienced.
Inside, the space was cozy, with shared tables and that quick, no-nonsense service Hong Kong cafés are famous for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lanzhou Noodle Soup on a Chilly Summer Night in Uralsk</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/lanzhou-noodle-soup-uralsk-kazakhstan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/lanzhou-noodle-soup-uralsk-kazakhstan/</guid>
      <description>In July 2025, during my first trip to Kazakhstan, I found myself in the small, quiet town of Uralsk. The days were impossibly long—sunset around 11 PM—and dinner had turned into a late-night ritual. One chilly evening, with the temperature hovering around 18°C, we finally decided to step out for a proper meal.
I&amp;rsquo;d seen Lanzhou noodle shops before—first in Almaty, then again in Astana—but somehow never got around to trying them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medium Draft - Tonkotsu Ramen Bangalore</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/medium-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/medium-draft/</guid>
      <description>I Found the Best Tonkotsu Ramen in Bangalore — And It&amp;rsquo;s Only 30 Bowls a Day How a small ramen shop in HSR Layout became my go-to comfort food spot after returning from Japan Ever since my 2023 trip to Japan, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a mission to find that same ramen magic here in Bangalore. The search ended at Tokyo Suzuki Ramen—a small, cozy spot hidden in HSR Layout that serves only 30 bowls a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof of Work</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/proof-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/proof-of-work/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning Jobs Platform - A platform connecting ML talent with companies worldwide. machinelearningjobs.dev
AI Travel Agent - An AI-powered travel agent. ai-travel-agent.fly.dev</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tonkotsu Ramen at Tokyo Suzuki Ramen, Bangalore, India</title>
      <link>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/tonkotsu-ramen-at-tokyo-suzuki-ramen-bangalore-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raunaqness.github.io/food/tonkotsu-ramen-at-tokyo-suzuki-ramen-bangalore-india/</guid>
      <description>Ever since my 2023 trip to Japan, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a mission to find that same ramen magic here in Bangalore. I found it at Tokyo Suzuki Ramen—a small, cozy spot hidden in HSR Layout.
The first time I tried their pork-based Tonkotsu Ramen, I was hooked. Rich, silky broth. Perfectly chewy noodles. Tender pork slices. Easily one of the best bowls I&amp;rsquo;ve had in India—and very well priced.
I loved it so much I brought my friends here… and now I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count of how many times I&amp;rsquo;ve been back.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
